<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Iwen Su</title>
    <link>https://iwensu0313.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Iwen Su</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 12 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://iwensu0313.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>NCEAS Roundtable Series, Santa Barbara, September 2018</title>
      <link>https://iwensu0313.github.io/post/ohi-fellows-roundtable/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iwensu0313.github.io/post/ohi-fellows-roundtable/</guid>
      <description>Presenter, &amp;ldquo;Ocean Health Index Global Fellows Program Seminar&amp;rdquo;, NCEAS Roundtable Series, Santa Barbara, September 2018.
Presented on the Ocean Health Index (OHI) Global Assessment framework, the open data science tools used in evaluating ocean health, the value of the fellowship program, and the data exploration dashboard I created for the OHI Mariculture goal.
PRESENTATION OVERVIEW:
The Ocean Health Index (OHI) Global Fellows Program is training the next generation of ocean data scientists through global ocean health assessments.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Conversation about Aquaculture, Santa Barbara, June 2018.</title>
      <link>https://iwensu0313.github.io/post/a-conversation-about-aquaculture/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iwensu0313.github.io/post/a-conversation-about-aquaculture/</guid>
      <description>Organizer, “A Conversation about Aquaculture”, student-led presentation series featuring local academic and industry experts in aquaculture, Bren School, Santa Barbara, June 2018.
Helped secure funding from various sources, outlined and monitored event budget, coordinated with guest speakers before, during, and after the event, and managed programming logistics.
EVENT OVERVIEW
Aquaculture is a fascinating industry that intersects with many different fields that we study here at Bren. We want to hold a ‘Night of Aquaculture’ to allow participants to explore a range of topics, discuss current industry direction and development, and to have the opportunity to connect with people based in California doing important work in the aquaculture space.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Seaweed Aquaculture in Southern California, Santa Barbara, March 2018.</title>
      <link>https://iwensu0313.github.io/post/seaweed-aquaculture-in-southern-california/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iwensu0313.github.io/post/seaweed-aquaculture-in-southern-california/</guid>
      <description>Presenter, “Testing the Economic Feasibility of Seaweed Aquaculture in Southern California,” Master Project Defenses, Bren School, Santa Barbara, March 2018.
Presented project scope and results to an academic panel. Presentations were open to the public.
PRESENTATION OVERVIEW:
Globally, aquaculture systems produce 23.8 million tonnes of seaweed, worth $6.4 billion USD annually. The majority of edible seaweeds consumed in California is imported from Asia and any local seaweed product is overwhelmingly sourced from wild harvesters in Northern California.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>VSE Mussel Farming Site Selection Workshop, Ventura, July 2017.</title>
      <link>https://iwensu0313.github.io/post/vse-mussel-farming-lease/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jul 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iwensu0313.github.io/post/vse-mussel-farming-lease/</guid>
      <description>Invited workshop participant, “Gathering Community Input on the Location of VSE Mussel Farming Lease Sites”, Ventura Shellfish Enterprise Site Selection Workshop, Ventura Harbor, July 2017.
Represented SeaSketch at the site selection workshop and collected public comments.
WORKSHOP OVERVIEW:
The Ventura Shellfish Enterprise (VSE) held a series of site selection workshops from July to August 2017. These collaborative and interactive workshops are aimed at gathering information from stakeholders to help evaluate and identify potential locations for mussel farming plots within a larger candidate growing area.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Seafood Traceability Forum, Los Angeles, April 2017.</title>
      <link>https://iwensu0313.github.io/post/presentations-workshops-rmd/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Apr 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iwensu0313.github.io/post/presentations-workshops-rmd/</guid>
      <description>Invited workshop participant, LMU-UCLA Seafood Traceability Forum, Loyola Marymount University, Los Angeles, April 2017.
Participated in forum breakout sessions to discuss various seafood traceability issues.
WORKSHOP OVERVIEW:
Developed in collaboration with scientists from LMU, UCLA, and various regulatory agencies, this forum will be an open discussion on the current state of seafood traceability in the Greater Los Angeles area, and will explore options for addressing the problem of seafood mislabeling.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>